affinitywater.co.uk 2015-09-06

# Affinity Water

## Information we collect

Affinity Water Limited is registered under the Data Protection Act 1998. Confidentiality and the privacy of customers and users of this website are of utmost importance to us. The information that we gather from you through this website is used by us to ensure that we can give you the best possible service and for our own internal market analysis.

Click here to view our Privacy policy >>

#### Protecting Personal Information

If you are a customer of Affinity Water and would like more information on how we protect your personal information please click here.

#### Communicating with us

If you send us a message by electronic mail it may be seen by a person other than the addressee.

We recognise the uncertainty that people have with sending information over the Internet. We will not send you unwanted e-mail messages or junk mail and your details will not be disclosed to any organisation beyond Affinity Water for marketing purposes without your explicit permission.

#### Encryption

Information transmitted through this website is encrypted and therefore cannot easily be intercepted by or electronically delivered to third parties.

#### Cookies

Our website uses cookies to distinguish you from other users of our website. This helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse our website and also allows us to improve our site.

**We use the following cookies:**

  * **Strictly necessary cookies:** These are cookies that are required for the operation of our website. They include, for example, cookies that enable you to log into secure areas of our website or make use of e-billing services.

  * **Analytical/performance cookies:** They allow us to recognise and count the number of visitors and to see how visitors move around our website when they are using it. This helps us to improve the way our website works, for example, by ensuring that users are finding what they are looking for easily.

Some of the pages within this website use Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”).

We use Google Analytics to analyse the use of this website. Google Analytics generates statistical and other information about website use by means of cookies, which are stored on users' computers. The information generated relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of the website. Google will store this information.

Google's privacy policy is available at: <http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html>.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

Most browsers allow you to reject all cookies, whilst some browsers allow you to reject just third party cookies. For example, in Internet Explorer you can refuse all cookies by clicking “Tools”, “Internet Options”, “Privacy”, and selecting “Block all cookies” using the sliding selector. Blocking all cookies will, however, have a negative impact upon the usability of many websites, including this one.

You can find more information about the individual cookies we use and the purposes for which we use them in the table below:

### **Cookie name**

| 

### **Originates From**

| 

### **Purpose**

| 

### **Type**  
  
---|---|---|---  
  
**ASP.NET**

| 

Affinity Water

| 

Identifies a user to the server, will issue a customer ID, active only whilst browsing.

| 

Session is closed when customer closes browser  
  
**__utma,_utmb, _utmc, _utmz, _utmv**

| 

Google Analytics

| 

Identify users, track website usage for google analytics, does not store any personal information. Allows us to improve our site based on customer experience.

| 

Persistent – various life spans from 30mins – 2 years  
  
**cookievalue**

| 

Synthetix (FAQ software)                                                                                                                                              

| 

Identifies a user, holds a randomly issued customer ID and session number, allows reporting on unique users of the software, so will not count the same user multiple times if they visit numerous times over a year period.

| 

Persistent – 1 year lifespan  
  
**Cookie’customerID’@addthis.com**

| 

Addthis (font size software)                                                           

| 

When a font size is selected using this widget, it will remember the selection along with the customer ID until it expires.

| 

Persistent – 1 year lifespan                                                                                                
  
You block cookies by activating the setting on your browser that allows you to refuse the setting of all or some cookies. However, if you use your browser settings to block all cookies (including essential cookies) you may not be able to access all or parts of our site.

#### Data Protection (Credit Reference and Fraud Prevention Agencies)

We may need to share your personal information with Credit Reference and Fraud Prevention agencies. For a guide to how the information may be used **please click here.**
